[
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> launched her first official fragrance , <MISC> in 2010 .",
        "s2": "In February 2011 , <ORG> launched her second fragrance , <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.933,
        "id": 12
    },
    {
        "s1": "In February 2011 , <ORG> launched her second fragrance , <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "s2": "<ORG> 's third fragrance , <MISC> , was launched in September 2011 .",
        "score": 0.905,
        "id": 14
    },
    {
        "s1": "On 17 May 2015 filming took place on the <LOC> in <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Filming then took place in <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.814,
        "id": 54
    },
    {
        "s1": "” <PER> <PER> from the <ORG> <ORG> , gave it a 75 grade .",
        "s2": "” <PER> <PER> over at the <ORG> <ORG> , gave it a 75 grade .",
        "score": 0.99,
        "id": 58
    },
    {
        "s1": "” <PER> <PER> from the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> , gave it an 80 grade , saying : “ <PER> is cruelly efficient .",
        "s2": "” <PER> <PER> from the <ORG> <ORG> , gave it a 75 grade .",
        "score": 0.784,
        "id": 56
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <LOC> <LOC> — a tidal strait — flows from <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> and separates the <LOC> and <LOC> from <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> <LOC> , another tidal strait between the East and <LOC> <LOC> , separates most of <LOC> from the <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.92,
        "id": 63
    },
    {
        "s1": "In 2012 , 6.3 % of <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> was of <MISC> ethnicity , with nearly three-fourths living in either <LOC> or <LOC> , geographically on <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<MISC> were the largest <MISC> <MISC> ethnic group at 0.8 % , followed by <MISC> , who made up 0.2 % of <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> 's population in 2010 .",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 66
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> made up 1.2 % of the city 's population , and <MISC> 0.3 % .",
        "s2": "<MISC> are the largest <MISC> <MISC> group , comprising 2.4 % of the city 's population , with <MISC> and <MISC> at 0.7 % and 0.5 % , respectively .",
        "score": 0.813,
        "id": 67
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> <MISC> number over 160,000 in <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> , with the highest concentration in <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<MISC> <MISC> are most highly concentrated in the <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.78,
        "id": 70
    },
    {
        "s1": "\" <MISC> \" , a single jointly produced with <PER> and <PER> , was released in January 2015 .",
        "s2": "In March 2015 , <ORG> released the single \" <MISC> <MISC> \" featuring <ORG> <ORG> , <PER> <PER> and <PER> <PER> .",
        "score": 0.869,
        "id": 95
    },
    {
        "s1": "West released a single , \" <MISC> <MISC> \" , featuring <PER> <PER> , on December 31 , 2014 .",
        "s2": "In March 2015 , <ORG> released the single \" <MISC> <MISC> \" featuring <ORG> <ORG> , <PER> <PER> and <PER> <PER> .",
        "score": 0.79,
        "id": 94
    },
    {
        "s1": "In <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> , devotion to the <MISC> <MISC> is the main practice .",
        "s2": "In <MISC> <MISC> , devotion to the <MISC> <MISC> is the main practice ..",
        "score": 0.994,
        "id": 104
    },
    {
        "s1": "In <LOC> , it is aired a few hours after the <LOC> telecast .",
        "s2": "It is also aired in <LOC> on <ORG> two days after the telecast .",
        "score": 0.857,
        "id": 119
    },
    {
        "s1": "In the <LOC> <LOC> , episodes are aired one day after the <LOC> broadcast on digital channel <ORG> .",
        "s2": "In <LOC> and <LOC> , the show airs two days after its original broadcast .",
        "score": 0.846,
        "id": 121
    },
    {
        "s1": "In <LOC> , it is aired a few hours after the <LOC> telecast .",
        "s2": "In the <LOC> <LOC> , episodes are aired one day after the <LOC> broadcast on digital channel <ORG> .",
        "score": 0.781,
        "id": 118
    },
    {
        "s1": "Dog meat is consumed in some <MISC> <MISC> countries , including <LOC> , <LOC> , and <LOC> , a practice that dates back to antiquity .",
        "s2": "Dog meat is also consumed in some parts of <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.846,
        "id": 129
    },
    {
        "s1": "Dog meat is consumed in some <MISC> <MISC> countries , including <LOC> , <LOC> , and <LOC> , a practice that dates back to antiquity .",
        "s2": "Other cultures , such as <LOC> and pre-Columbian <LOC> , also consumed dog meat in their history .",
        "score": 0.819,
        "id": 127
    },
    {
        "s1": "Process theology typically stresses <PER> 's relational nature .",
        "s2": "a process theology without <PER> ..",
        "score": 0.811,
        "id": 137
    },
    {
        "s1": "( <LOC> ) , M.Sc .",
        "s2": ") , M.Sc .",
        "score": 0.826,
        "id": 148
    },
    {
        "s1": "The first polytechnic in <LOC> <LOC> is <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> , established in 1972 through upgrading the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> ( <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> before 1947 ) .",
        "s2": "The second polytechnic , the <ORG> <ORG> of <LOC> <LOC> , was founded in 1984 .",
        "score": 0.845,
        "id": 152
    },
    {
        "s1": "In recent years , <ORG> <ORG> is reorganized as <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> and 2 institutes of technology were founded in <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "In 2010 , another technical university named <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> was founded in <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.796,
        "id": 157
    },
    {
        "s1": "Of the <MISC> <MISC> languages , the better understood and recorded ones are <MISC> <MISC> ( a language of <LOC> <LOC> ) and <MISC> ( the language of the <MISC> ) .",
        "s2": "<MISC> <MISC> languages included <MISC> <MISC> ( a language of <LOC> <LOC> ) , <MISC> , and <MISC> ..",
        "score": 0.863,
        "id": 163
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> languages or <MISC> languages form a branch of the <MISC> languages , which in turn are a branch of the <MISC> language family .",
        "s2": "Of the <MISC> <MISC> languages , the better understood and recorded ones are <MISC> <MISC> ( a language of <LOC> <LOC> ) and <MISC> ( the language of the <MISC> ) .",
        "score": 0.765,
        "id": 161
    },
    {
        "s1": "All <MISC> languages are descended from a common ancestor , <MISC> .",
        "s2": "In turn , and together with <MISC> and the <MISC> languages , <MISC> descends from a common ancestor <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.879,
        "id": 165
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> script was first <MISC> in the 1920s under the then <MISC> nationality policy .",
        "s2": "The script was however subsequently <MISC> in the 1930s by the <MISC> government ..",
        "score": 0.792,
        "id": 172
    },
    {
        "s1": "He was joined by <PER> <PER> , who became the chairman and CEO of <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> became the new CEO of the <ORG> <ORG> unit .",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 202
    },
    {
        "s1": "On August 5 , 2008 , <ORG> and <ORG> announced that <ORG> had agreed to acquire <ORG> 's 50 % stake in <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "<ORG> completed its acquisition of <ORG> 's 50 % stake in the companies' joint venture on October 1 , 2008 .",
        "score": 0.845,
        "id": 204
    },
    {
        "s1": "In May 2014 , the <ORG> <ORG> announced <LOC> <LOC> had an estimated population of 620,602 in 2014 and that it had grown 5.3 percent between April 2010 and June 2013 .",
        "s2": "The 2014 estimate of 620,602 is the largest population <LOC> <LOC> has ever recorded .",
        "score": 0.776,
        "id": 209
    },
    {
        "s1": "However , it is true that in a small minority of cases , women hunt the same kind of quarry as men , sometimes doing so alongside men .",
        "s2": "According to one study , \" About 85 % of <MISC> <MISC> women hunt , and they hunt the same quarry as men .",
        "score": 0.848,
        "id": 216
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> was replaced by then-Vice Chairman <PER> <PER> and <ORG> <ORG> head <PER> <PER> .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> was also upped to co-chairperson .",
        "score": 0.785,
        "id": 222
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> was replaced by then-Vice Chairman <PER> <PER> and <ORG> <ORG> head <PER> <PER> .",
        "s2": "In September 2013 , <PER> <PER> was ousted as co-chairman of <ORG> <ORG> , promoting <PER> <PER> to sole-chairman .",
        "score": 0.757,
        "id": 223
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> <PER> attempted the first comprehensive history of <MISC> comics with <ORG> <ORG> ( 1947 ) .",
        "s2": "<MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ( 1985 ) and <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ( 1993 ) were early attempts in <MISC> to formalize the study of comics .",
        "score": 0.825,
        "id": 227
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ( 1985 ) and <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ( 1993 ) were early attempts in <MISC> to formalize the study of comics .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> 's <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ( 2000 ) was the first full-length treatment of comics from a philosophical perspective .",
        "score": 0.825,
        "id": 229
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> <PER> attempted the first comprehensive history of <MISC> comics with <ORG> <ORG> ( 1947 ) .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> 's <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ( 2000 ) was the first full-length treatment of comics from a philosophical perspective .",
        "score": 0.798,
        "id": 228
    },
    {
        "s1": "Early web browsers supported only a very simple version of <MISC> .",
        "s2": "Modern web browsers support a combination of standards-based and de facto <MISC> and <MISC> , which should be rendered in the same way by all browsers ..",
        "score": 0.812,
        "id": 243
    },
    {
        "s1": "It is named after the <MISC> <MISC> constellation , which is known in <MISC> as <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The name literally means \" <MISC> <MISC> \" , the name given by ancient <MISC> astronomers to the seven brightest stars of the <LOC> <LOC> constellation .",
        "score": 0.824,
        "id": 256
    },
    {
        "s1": "The first satellite , <MISC> , was launched on October 31 , 2000 .",
        "s2": "The second satellite , <MISC> , was successfully launched on December 21 , 2000 .",
        "score": 0.86,
        "id": 259
    },
    {
        "s1": "E.g.",
        "s2": "E.g.",
        "score": 1.0,
        "id": 266
    },
    {
        "s1": "E.g.",
        "s2": "E.g.",
        "score": 1.0,
        "id": 268
    },
    {
        "s1": "In nouns and adjectives , maintenance of / n / of medieval plurals in proparoxytone words .",
        "s2": "In nouns and adjectives , loss of / n / of medieval plurals in proparoxytone words .",
        "score": 0.936,
        "id": 267
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> belongs to the <MISC> branch of the <MISC> languages , along with <MISC> , <MISC> , and other nearby languages .",
        "s2": "<MISC> is distantly related to <MISC> and to the <MISC> languages ..",
        "score": 0.914,
        "id": 271
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> belongs to the <MISC> branch of the <MISC> languages , along with <MISC> , <MISC> , and other nearby languages .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> languages do not belong to the <MISC> languages .",
        "score": 0.792,
        "id": 270
    },
    {
        "s1": "Modern <MISC> orthography is based on the <MISC> <MISC> created by <PER> <PER> in the second half of the 19th century based on <MISC> orthography .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> <MISC> it replaced was created in the 17th century by <PER> <PER> <PER> and <PER> <PER> based on standard <MISC> orthography .",
        "score": 0.834,
        "id": 274
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> then switched to a neutral-site championship , with <ORG> <ORG> and <ORG> in <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<ORG> <ORG> returned to a neutral site and was once again played in <LOC> <LOC> , where the <ORG> returned and defeated the <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "score": 0.79,
        "id": 279
    },
    {
        "s1": "<ORG> <ORG> in <LOC> <LOC> was deemed a success , and the city was chosen to host <ORG> <ORG> , in which the <ORG> <ORG> defeated the defending champion <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "In <ORG> <ORG> , the <ORG> <ORG> defeated the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> at their home arena , <LOC> <LOC> , in <LOC> , <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.766,
        "id": 280
    },
    {
        "s1": "The first video game based on the <ORG> was <MISC> <MISC> for the <ORG> released in 1988 .",
        "s2": "<ORG> <ORG> released another <ORG> video game , titled <MISC> <MISC> : <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> , on February 21 , 2007 , for the <MISC> <MISC> ..",
        "score": 0.802,
        "id": 282
    },
    {
        "s1": "Eleven of the seventeen teams in operation in 2007 had average attendance figures over 13,000 .",
        "s2": "In 2008 , the overall attendance average increased to 12,957 , with eight teams exceeding 13,000 per game ..",
        "score": 0.793,
        "id": 285
    },
    {
        "s1": "As such , there is no single universally agreed scientific meaning of the word \" matter \" .",
        "s2": "Scientifically , the term \" mass \" is well-defined , but \" matter \" is not .",
        "score": 0.786,
        "id": 288
    },
    {
        "s1": "Different fields of science use the term matter in different , and sometimes incompatible , ways .",
        "s2": "As such , there is no single universally agreed scientific meaning of the word \" matter \" .",
        "score": 0.781,
        "id": 287
    },
    {
        "s1": "16,413 people were employed in the secondary sector and there were 950 businesses in this sector .",
        "s2": "135,973 people were employed in the tertiary sector , with 7,654 businesses in this sector ..",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 300
    },
    {
        "s1": "Of the kindergarten pupils , 32.4 % were permanent or temporary residents of <LOC> ( not citizens ) and 40.2 % have a different mother language than the classroom language .",
        "s2": "Of the primary pupils , 30.1 % were permanent or temporary residents of <LOC> ( not citizens ) and 35.7 % have a different mother language than the classroom language .",
        "score": 0.938,
        "id": 302
    },
    {
        "s1": "Of the primary pupils , 30.1 % were permanent or temporary residents of <LOC> ( not citizens ) and 35.7 % have a different mother language than the classroom language .",
        "s2": "There were 28.7 % who were permanent or temporary residents of <LOC> ( not citizens ) and 32.7 % have a different mother language than the classroom language ..",
        "score": 0.913,
        "id": 304
    },
    {
        "s1": "Of the kindergarten pupils , 32.4 % were permanent or temporary residents of <LOC> ( not citizens ) and 40.2 % have a different mother language than the classroom language .",
        "s2": "There were 28.7 % who were permanent or temporary residents of <LOC> ( not citizens ) and 32.7 % have a different mother language than the classroom language ..",
        "score": 0.88,
        "id": 303
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> <MISC> supports at most two start and end rules per time zone setting .",
        "s2": "Older <MISC> <MISC> systems usually store only a single start and end rule for each zone , so that the same <MISC> setting reliably supports only post-2006 time stamps ..",
        "score": 0.82,
        "id": 307
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> use the <MISC> alphabet and the <MISC> <MISC> use <MISC> alphabet , the <MISC> who are <MISC> also use the <MISC> .",
        "s2": "Few <MISC> <MISC> and <MISC> <MISC> use the <MISC> alphabet however .",
        "score": 0.892,
        "id": 319
    },
    {
        "s1": "Few <MISC> <MISC> and <MISC> <MISC> use the <MISC> alphabet however .",
        "s2": "There is also a <MISC> script to write in <MISC> , called the <MISC> alphabet ..",
        "score": 0.843,
        "id": 323
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> use the <MISC> alphabet and the <MISC> <MISC> use <MISC> alphabet , the <MISC> who are <MISC> also use the <MISC> .",
        "s2": "There is also a <MISC> script to write in <MISC> , called the <MISC> alphabet ..",
        "score": 0.833,
        "id": 321
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> use the <MISC> alphabet and the <MISC> <MISC> use <MISC> alphabet , the <MISC> who are <MISC> also use the <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> language and <MISC> language uses both <MISC> and <MISC> alphabets .",
        "score": 0.778,
        "id": 320
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <LOC> <LOC> runs along the western border of the city , separating it from the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> <LOC> runs through the middle of the city and is bridged in several places .",
        "score": 0.835,
        "id": 325
    },
    {
        "s1": "The northernmost bridge , and the first to be built , is at <LOC> , where the <LOC> road crosses the <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The southernmost , and newest , bridge on the <LOC> is the <LOC> <LOC> , which is a toll bridge ..",
        "score": 0.809,
        "id": 327
    },
    {
        "s1": "Further south is <LOC> <LOC> which is notable as it was opened as a free bridge ( it was originally named the <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> ) , and was never a toll bridge .",
        "s2": "The southernmost , and newest , bridge on the <LOC> is the <LOC> <LOC> , which is a toll bridge ..",
        "score": 0.775,
        "id": 328
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <LOC> motorway links the city to <LOC> and also , via a link to the <LOC> ( part of the <MISC> route E05 ) at <LOC> , with the <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> motorway is a spur of the <LOC> , linking it with the <LOC> <LOC> and city centre ..",
        "score": 0.862,
        "id": 332
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <LOC> motorway , linking places along the south coast of <LOC> , runs just to the north of the city .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> motorway is a spur of the <LOC> , linking it with the <LOC> <LOC> and city centre ..",
        "score": 0.806,
        "id": 331
    },
    {
        "s1": "A treaty is an agreement under international law entered into by actors in international law , namely sovereign states and international organizations .",
        "s2": "A treaty may also be known as an ( international ) agreement , protocol , covenant , convention , pact , or exchange of letters , among other terms .",
        "score": 0.777,
        "id": 335
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> , <MISC> , <MISC> ...",
        "s2": "<MISC> ( with a <MISC> accent ) ...",
        "score": 0.774,
        "id": 341
    },
    {
        "s1": "This may be consistent with the theory that in <MISC> <LOC> is a name of <MISC> origin ( which is common for prominent mountains and mountain ranges in the <LOC> region ) .",
        "s2": "In <MISC> times , \" <LOC> \" was a name for the eastern <LOC> , while in the <MISC> language \" <LOC> \" ( or \" <LOC> \") was occasionally used as a name for <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 354
    },
    {
        "s1": "Housekeeping genes are critical for carrying out basic cell functions and so are expressed at a relatively constant level ( constitutively ) .",
        "s2": "Not all essential genes are housekeeping genes since some essential genes are developmentally regulated or expressed at certain times during the organism 's life cycle ..",
        "score": 0.834,
        "id": 362
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> is split into two segments .",
        "s2": "The second segment of <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> begins at <LOC> <LOC> , at <LOC> <LOC> of <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.853,
        "id": 370
    },
    {
        "s1": "The second segment of <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> begins at <LOC> <LOC> , at <LOC> <LOC> of <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> , which is located on <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> between <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.834,
        "id": 373
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> is split into two segments .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> , which is located on <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> between <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.783,
        "id": 371
    },
    {
        "s1": "The relationship between brain size , body size and other variables has been studied across a wide range of vertebrate species .",
        "s2": "In general , smaller animals tend to have larger brains , measured as a fraction of body size .",
        "score": 0.812,
        "id": 379
    },
    {
        "s1": "Brains are most simply compared in terms of their size .",
        "s2": "In general , smaller animals tend to have larger brains , measured as a fraction of body size .",
        "score": 0.785,
        "id": 377
    },
    {
        "s1": "The relationship between brain size , body size and other variables has been studied across a wide range of vertebrate species .",
        "s2": "As a rule , brain size increases with body size , but not in a simple linear proportion .",
        "score": 0.765,
        "id": 378
    },
    {
        "s1": "<ORG> recognizes neither a <LOC> <LOC> nor a <LOC> <LOC> , dividing the countries instead among three regions : <LOC> <LOC> , <LOC> and the <LOC> , and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "\" The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> defines <LOC> <LOC> to contain the countries included elsewhere in the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.806,
        "id": 391
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some of the <MISC> refugees from north <LOC> might have resided in areas near <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Some refugees from the north <LOC> might have found residence in south <LOC> depending on their social status and military power in the north .",
        "score": 0.848,
        "id": 397
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some of the <MISC> refugees from north <LOC> might have resided in areas near <LOC> .",
        "s2": "It suggests that a small number of powerful , elite <MISC> refugees from the <LOC> <LOC> might have taken refugee in south of the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.792,
        "id": 396
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some may have lost social privilege , and took refugee in areas south to <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Some refugees from the north <LOC> might have found residence in south <LOC> depending on their social status and military power in the north .",
        "score": 0.776,
        "id": 395
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some may have lost social privilege , and took refugee in areas south to <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "It suggests that a small number of powerful , elite <MISC> refugees from the <LOC> <LOC> might have taken refugee in south of the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.77,
        "id": 394
    },
    {
        "s1": "The 1080i25 or 1080i50 notation identifies interlaced scanning format with 25 frames ( 50 fields ) per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "s2": "The 1080i30 or 1080i60 notation identifies interlaced scanning format with 30 frames ( 60 fields ) per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "score": 0.914,
        "id": 403
    },
    {
        "s1": "For example , 1920 × 1080p25 identifies progressive scanning format with 25 frames per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "s2": "The 1080i25 or 1080i50 notation identifies interlaced scanning format with 25 frames ( 50 fields ) per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "score": 0.855,
        "id": 400
    },
    {
        "s1": "The 1080i30 or 1080i60 notation identifies interlaced scanning format with 30 frames ( 60 fields ) per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "s2": "The 720p60 notation identifies progressive scanning format with 60 frames per second , each frame being 720 pixels high ; 1,280 pixels horizontally are implied ..",
        "score": 0.85,
        "id": 405
    },
    {
        "s1": "For example , 1920 × 1080p25 identifies progressive scanning format with 25 frames per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "s2": "The 720p60 notation identifies progressive scanning format with 60 frames per second , each frame being 720 pixels high ; 1,280 pixels horizontally are implied ..",
        "score": 0.819,
        "id": 402
    },
    {
        "s1": "For example , 1920 × 1080p25 identifies progressive scanning format with 25 frames per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "s2": "The 1080i30 or 1080i60 notation identifies interlaced scanning format with 30 frames ( 60 fields ) per second , each frame being 1,920 pixels wide and 1,080 pixels high .",
        "score": 0.811,
        "id": 401
    },
    {
        "s1": "Within the same species the cross-sectional area of the sapwood is very roughly proportional to the size of the crown of the tree .",
        "s2": "Sapwood is thicker in the upper portion of the trunk of a tree than near the base , because the age and the diameter of the upper sections are less ..",
        "score": 0.809,
        "id": 410
    },
    {
        "s1": "As the tree gets larger , the sapwood must necessarily become thinner or increase materially in volume .",
        "s2": "Sapwood is thicker in the upper portion of the trunk of a tree than near the base , because the age and the diameter of the upper sections are less ..",
        "score": 0.795,
        "id": 411
    },
    {
        "s1": "Hardwood lignin is primarily derived from sinapyl alcohol and coniferyl alcohol .",
        "s2": "Softwood lignin is mainly derived from coniferyl alcohol ..",
        "score": 0.869,
        "id": 419
    },
    {
        "s1": "In chemical terms , the difference between hardwood and softwood is reflected in the composition of the constituent lignin .",
        "s2": "Softwood lignin is mainly derived from coniferyl alcohol ..",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 418
    },
    {
        "s1": "The Middle Ages is the middle period of the three traditional divisions of <MISC> history : Antiquity , <MISC> period , and <MISC> period .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> period is itself subdivided into the Early , the High , and the Late Middle Ages ..",
        "score": 0.805,
        "id": 428
    },
    {
        "s1": "526 ) and set up a kingdom marked by its co-operation between the <MISC> and the <MISC> , at least until the last years of <PER> 's reign .",
        "s2": "509 – 511 ) , the <MISC> kingdom expanded and converted to <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.758,
        "id": 431
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> was gradually replaced by languages based on , but distinct from , <MISC> , collectively known as <MISC> languages .",
        "s2": "<MISC> remained the language of the <LOC> <LOC> , but the migrations of the <MISC> added <MISC> languages to <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.781,
        "id": 434
    },
    {
        "s1": "c.",
        "s2": "c.",
        "score": 1.0,
        "id": 436
    },
    {
        "s1": "c.",
        "s2": "c.",
        "score": 1.0,
        "id": 452
    },
    {
        "s1": "1374 ) and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1464 ) and <PER> <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.891,
        "id": 450
    },
    {
        "s1": "1374 ) and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1386 ) in <LOC> , and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.835,
        "id": 449
    },
    {
        "s1": "1374 ) and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1400 ) and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.829,
        "id": 448
    },
    {
        "s1": "1321 ) , <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1374 ) and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.824,
        "id": 445
    },
    {
        "s1": "1321 ) , <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1464 ) and <PER> <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.81,
        "id": 447
    },
    {
        "s1": "1400 ) and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1464 ) and <PER> <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.807,
        "id": 451
    },
    {
        "s1": "1386 ) in <LOC> , and <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "s2": "1464 ) and <PER> <PER> <PER> ( d.",
        "score": 0.787,
        "id": 453
    },
    {
        "s1": "1506 ) in 1492 that discovered the <LOC> .",
        "s2": "1498 ) in 1497 , which landed on <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.866,
        "id": 457
    },
    {
        "s1": "1524 ) sailed around <LOC> to <LOC> in 1498 .",
        "s2": "1498 ) in 1497 , which landed on <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.821,
        "id": 456
    },
    {
        "s1": "1524 ) sailed around <LOC> to <LOC> in 1498 .",
        "s2": "1506 ) in 1492 that discovered the <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.791,
        "id": 455
    },
    {
        "s1": "Bugs are usually not the fault of the computer .",
        "s2": "Since computers merely execute the instructions they are given , bugs are nearly always the result of programmer error or an oversight made in the program 's design ..",
        "score": 0.772,
        "id": 462
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> immunology courses include an Introductory Course and an Advance Course .",
        "s2": "The Introductory Course is a course that gives students an overview of the basics of immunology ..",
        "score": 0.924,
        "id": 486
    },
    {
        "s1": "Most graduate immunology schools follow the <ORG> courses immunology which are offered throughout numerous schools in the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> immunology courses include an Introductory Course and an Advance Course .",
        "score": 0.873,
        "id": 484
    },
    {
        "s1": "An additional extension to <MISC> is named <MISC> audio , as <MISC> already had a different meaning .",
        "s2": "<MISC> is thus an unofficial or proprietary extension to the MP3 format ..",
        "score": 0.777,
        "id": 488
    },
    {
        "s1": "House music is a genre of electronic dance music that originated in <LOC> in the early 1980s .",
        "s2": "Since the early to mid-1990s , house music has been infused in mainstream pop and dance music worldwide ..",
        "score": 0.838,
        "id": 497
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> is ranked eighth most populous city in the country and <LOC> <LOC> was ranked 16th most populous in <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( along with <LOC> <LOC> ) is the only state in <LOC> to have two cities ranked in the top 20 most populated .",
        "score": 0.8,
        "id": 501
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> has the <ORG> 's first retractable-roof stadium with natural grass , <LOC> <LOC> ( home of the <ORG> ) .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> <LOC> is also a retractable-roof stadium .",
        "score": 0.811,
        "id": 509
    },
    {
        "s1": "Blacks or <MISC> <MISC> made up 25 % of <LOC> 's population .",
        "s2": "<MISC> <MISC> made up 0.7 % of the population .",
        "score": 0.817,
        "id": 512
    },
    {
        "s1": "Blacks or <MISC> <MISC> made up 25 % of <LOC> 's population .",
        "s2": "In addition , <MISC> made up 37.4 % of <LOC> 's population while non-Hispanic whites made up 30.8 % , down from 62.4 % in 1970 ..",
        "score": 0.812,
        "id": 513
    },
    {
        "s1": "Bronze artifacts from the <MISC> culture date to 4500 <MISC> .",
        "s2": "<MISC> and <MISC> artifacts of copper and bronze alloys date to 3000 <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.816,
        "id": 516
    },
    {
        "s1": "An exclusive boundary arises , for example , when a person adopts a marker that imposes restrictions on the behaviour of others .",
        "s2": "An inclusive boundary is created , by contrast , by the use of a marker with which other people are ready and able to associate .",
        "score": 0.808,
        "id": 521
    },
    {
        "s1": "Boundaries can be inclusive or exclusive depending on how they are perceived by other people .",
        "s2": "At the same time , however , an inclusive boundary will also impose restrictions on the people it has included by limiting their inclusion within other boundaries .",
        "score": 0.777,
        "id": 520
    },
    {
        "s1": "Two of the main <MISC> communities in the <LOC> <LOC> are located in <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "There are also sizable and rapidly growing <MISC> communities throughout <LOC> <LOC> , particularly in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , and <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.801,
        "id": 534
    },
    {
        "s1": "Two of the main <MISC> communities in the <LOC> <LOC> are located in <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "In <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> , the neighborhoods of <LOC> <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , and <LOC> <LOC> , located in the borough of <LOC> , have particularly large <MISC> communities .",
        "score": 0.791,
        "id": 533
    },
    {
        "s1": "The process of making beer is known as brewing .",
        "s2": "A company that makes beer is called either a brewery or a brewing company .",
        "score": 0.8,
        "id": 536
    },
    {
        "s1": "Hops are added during boiling as a source of bitterness , flavour and aroma .",
        "s2": "The longer the hops are boiled , the more bitterness they contribute , but the less hop flavour and aroma remains in the beer ..",
        "score": 0.817,
        "id": 543
    },
    {
        "s1": "In 2002 <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> bought the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> to found <ORG> , becoming the second largest brewery , after <MISC> <MISC> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "In 2004 the <MISC> <ORG> was the third largest brewery by volume and the <MISC> <ORG> was the fifth largest .",
        "score": 0.806,
        "id": 545
    },
    {
        "s1": "In 2008 , <ORG> ( the second-largest ) bought <ORG> ( the third largest ) , the new <ORG> <ORG> company became again the largest brewer in the world .",
        "s2": "As of 2015 [ update ] <ORG> <ORG> is the largest brewery , with <ORG> second , and <ORG> <ORG> third ..",
        "score": 0.79,
        "id": 547
    },
    {
        "s1": "The word \" dollar \" is one of the words in the first paragraph of <MISC> <MISC> of Article 1 of the <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "In that context , \" dollars \" is a reference to the <MISC> milled dollar , a coin that had a monetary value of 8 <MISC> units of currency , or reales .",
        "score": 0.795,
        "id": 551
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> is <LOC> 's big theatre for musicals , shows and guest performances .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> is another big theatre in <LOC> , which also has an own Musical-Company .",
        "score": 0.902,
        "id": 561
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> <ORG> , the <ORG> ( <ORG> <ORG> ) , the <MISC> , the <MISC> and the <ORG> <ORG> belong to the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> <ORG> ( <ORG> <ORG> ) is the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "score": 0.792,
        "id": 560
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> is <LOC> 's big theatre for musicals , shows and guest performances .",
        "s2": "Some of the most important Musical-Productions are the rock musicals of the <MISC> rock musician <PER> <PER> <PER> , which take place at the <ORG> in the <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.759,
        "id": 562
    },
    {
        "s1": "On 17 May , the club clinched their 23rd <MISC> <MISC> title after defeating <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "On 30 May , the club defeated <ORG> <ORG> in the <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> final at <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.767,
        "id": 575
    },
    {
        "s1": "There is no single definition of an \" aircraft carrier \" , and modern navies use several variants of the type .",
        "s2": "These variants are sometimes categorized as sub-types of aircraft carriers , and sometimes as distinct types of naval aviation-capable ships .",
        "score": 0.787,
        "id": 579
    },
    {
        "s1": "On November 22 , 2005 , <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> was re-launched with the release of the <MISC> <MISC> , in which it was now integrated with the <MISC> <MISC> 's dashboard .",
        "s2": "On March 24 , 2010 , <ORG> introduced the <ORG> <ORG> to <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.816,
        "id": 589
    },
    {
        "s1": "The invasion of <LOC> was a debacle , though concurrent wars with <MISC> <MISC> on the western front ( <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ) were more successful .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> <LOC> invasion was a fiasco after the much larger <MISC> army retreated to <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.798,
        "id": 592
    },
    {
        "s1": "The term \" <LOC> <LOC> \" , for the region west of about the 96th or 98th meridian and east of the <LOC> <LOC> , was not generally used before the early 20th century .",
        "s2": "Today the term \" <LOC> <LOC> \" is used for a subregion of the <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.818,
        "id": 598
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> <PER> 's 1916 study , Physiographic Subdivision of the <LOC> <LOC> , brought the term <LOC> <LOC> into more widespread usage .",
        "s2": "Today the term \" <LOC> <LOC> \" is used for a subregion of the <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.77,
        "id": 599
    },
    {
        "s1": "Before that the region was almost invariably called the <LOC> <LOC> , in contrast to the lower <LOC> <LOC> of the <MISC> states .",
        "s2": "Today the term \" <LOC> <LOC> \" is used for a subregion of the <LOC> <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.757,
        "id": 600
    },
    {
        "s1": "One of the most widely used definitions defines it in terms of the variability within species , between species , and between ecosystems .",
        "s2": "This can refer to genetic variation , ecosystem variation , or species variation ( number of species ) within an area , biome , or planet .",
        "score": 0.76,
        "id": 603
    },
    {
        "s1": "Inhibition of gastrin and gastric acid secretion is lifted .",
        "s2": "This triggers G cells to release gastrin , which in turn stimulates parietal cells to secrete gastric acid .",
        "score": 0.793,
        "id": 610
    },
    {
        "s1": "Inhibition of gastrin and gastric acid secretion is lifted .",
        "s2": "This triggers intestinal gastrin to be released .",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 611
    },
    {
        "s1": "In the 1927 case <PER> v .",
        "s2": "In the 1939 case <PER> v .",
        "score": 0.853,
        "id": 612
    },
    {
        "s1": "An executive assistant director manages each branch .",
        "s2": "Each branch is then divided into offices and divisions , each headed by an assistant director .",
        "score": 0.815,
        "id": 615
    },
    {
        "s1": "The two main aspects of identity development are self-clarity and self-esteem .",
        "s2": "[ citation needed ] Researchers have used three general approaches to understanding identity development : self-concept , sense of identity , and self-esteem .",
        "score": 0.876,
        "id": 624
    },
    {
        "s1": "Identity development is a stage in the adolescent life cycle .",
        "s2": "The environment in which an adolescent grows up also plays an important role in their identity development .",
        "score": 0.84,
        "id": 623
    },
    {
        "s1": "Identity development is a stage in the adolescent life cycle .",
        "s2": "[ citation needed ] Researchers have used three general approaches to understanding identity development : self-concept , sense of identity , and self-esteem .",
        "score": 0.776,
        "id": 622
    },
    {
        "s1": "Identity development is a stage in the adolescent life cycle .",
        "s2": "But , developing and maintaining identity ( in adolescent years ) is a difficult task due to multiple factors such as family life , environment , and social status .",
        "score": 0.776,
        "id": 620
    },
    {
        "s1": "Divorce usually results in less contact between the adolescent and their noncustodial parent .",
        "s2": "A parental divorce during childhood or adolescence continues to have a negative effect when a person is in his or her twenties and early thirties .",
        "score": 0.774,
        "id": 628
    },
    {
        "s1": "Romantic relationships tend to increase in prevalence throughout adolescence .",
        "s2": "By age 15 , 53 % of adolescents have had a romantic relationship that lasted at least one month over the course of the previous 18 months .",
        "score": 0.812,
        "id": 629
    },
    {
        "s1": "Romantic relationships tend to increase in prevalence throughout adolescence .",
        "s2": "Overall , positive romantic relationships among adolescents can result in long-term benefits .",
        "score": 0.795,
        "id": 630
    },
    {
        "s1": "For instance , some cultures find teenage sexual activity acceptable but teenage pregnancy highly undesirable .",
        "s2": "Other cultures do not object to teenage sexual activity or teenage pregnancy , as long as they occur after marriage .",
        "score": 0.837,
        "id": 634
    },
    {
        "s1": "In less restrictive cultures , there is more tolerance for displays of adolescent sexuality , or of the interaction between males and females in public and private spaces .",
        "s2": "Less restrictive cultures may tolerate some aspects of adolescent sexuality , while objecting to other aspects .",
        "score": 0.825,
        "id": 632
    },
    {
        "s1": "The relationships adolescents have with their peers , family , and members of their social sphere play a vital role in the social development of an adolescent .",
        "s2": "Relationships are vital in the social development of an adolescent due to the extreme influence peers can have over an individual .",
        "score": 0.798,
        "id": 639
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some men do not develop full facial hair for 10 years after puberty .",
        "s2": "Facial hair continues to get coarser , darker and thicker for another 2 – 4 years after puberty ..",
        "score": 0.77,
        "id": 642
    },
    {
        "s1": "During early adolescence , adolescents often associate in cliques , exclusive , single-sex groups of peers with whom they are particularly close .",
        "s2": "Towards late adolescence , cliques often merge into mixed-sex groups as teenagers begin romantically engaging with one another .",
        "score": 0.84,
        "id": 647
    },
    {
        "s1": "Adolescents tend to associate with \" cliques \" on a small scale and \" crowds \" on a larger scale .",
        "s2": "Despite the common notion that cliques are an inherently negative influence , they may help adolescents become socially acclimated and form a stronger sense of identity .",
        "score": 0.823,
        "id": 645
    },
    {
        "s1": "Adolescents tend to associate with \" cliques \" on a small scale and \" crowds \" on a larger scale .",
        "s2": "During early adolescence , adolescents often associate in cliques , exclusive , single-sex groups of peers with whom they are particularly close .",
        "score": 0.784,
        "id": 644
    },
    {
        "s1": "It was released to the public in September 2000 , as the <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> , featuring a revamped user interface called \" <MISC> \" .",
        "s2": "The initial version of <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> , 10.0 \" <MISC> \" , was released on March 24 , 2001 .",
        "score": 0.871,
        "id": 660
    },
    {
        "s1": "Sometime between the fourth and eighth centuries , the <MISC> script , derived from <MISC> , became prevalent .",
        "s2": "The latter was displaced in its turn by <PER> in the 11th or 12th century , with intermediary stages such as the <MISC> script .",
        "score": 0.792,
        "id": 672
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> evolved into a multiplicity of <MISC> scripts , many of which were used to write <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The latter was displaced in its turn by <PER> in the 11th or 12th century , with intermediary stages such as the <MISC> script .",
        "score": 0.765,
        "id": 671
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> lost 39 officers and 1,076 men .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> lost 36 officers and 1,060 men .",
        "score": 0.975,
        "id": 689
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> lost 19 officers , a surgeon and 431 men out of a total of 700 .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> lost 39 officers and 1,076 men .",
        "score": 0.849,
        "id": 687
    },
    {
        "s1": "Uranium is a naturally occurring element that can be found in low levels within all rock , soil , and water .",
        "s2": "Uranium is also the highest-numbered element to be found naturally in significant quantities on <LOC> and is almost always found combined with other elements .",
        "score": 0.799,
        "id": 691
    },
    {
        "s1": "Individuals suffering from substance abuse display disrupted rhythms .",
        "s2": "These disrupted rhythms can increase the risk for substance abuse and relapse .",
        "score": 0.802,
        "id": 702
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> <PER> remains under a death sentence in <LOC> for the crime of \" kidnapping with bodily injury .",
        "s2": "<PER> was never charged with the murder of <PER> in <LOC> , but was sentenced to death by a jury in <LOC> for \" kidnapping with bodily injury .",
        "score": 0.823,
        "id": 711
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> , however , executed 40 percent of those sentenced , which was about four times higher than the national average .",
        "s2": "<LOC> had executed only 1 percent of those sentenced ..",
        "score": 0.805,
        "id": 716
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> gave 2 percent of murderers a death sentence , less than the national average .",
        "s2": "<LOC> , however , executed 40 percent of those sentenced , which was about four times higher than the national average .",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 715
    },
    {
        "s1": "The last execution of a juvenile may have been <PER> <PER> , who died in the <LOC> gas chamber on April 10 , 1959 , at the age of 17 .",
        "s2": "The last person to be executed for a crime committed as a juvenile was <PER> <PER> on April 3 , 2003 in <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.765,
        "id": 721
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> <PER> in a rough calculation of <MISC> and <MISC> <MISC> , implies that <MISC> make up less than 74 % of <MISC> worldwide .",
        "s2": "Other estimates place <MISC> <MISC> as making up about 75 % of <MISC> worldwide ..",
        "score": 0.807,
        "id": 728
    },
    {
        "s1": "A study of haplotypes of the Y-chromosome , published in 2000 , addressed the paternal origins of <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "s2": "found that the Y-chromosome of <MISC> and <MISC> <MISC> contained mutations that are also common among <MISC> <MISC> peoples , but uncommon in the general <MISC> population .",
        "score": 0.8,
        "id": 733
    },
    {
        "s1": "Eccl.",
        "s2": "Eccl.",
        "score": 1.0,
        "id": 737
    },
    {
        "s1": "The Gospel of <PER> and particularly the first chapter demonstrates the Divinity of <PER> .",
        "s2": "The Gospel of <PER> 's first chapter began to be said at the end of <LOC> , we believe as a result of <PER> , and his life 's stand , but quietly .",
        "score": 0.793,
        "id": 739
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> relocated to <LOC> , <LOC> and became the <ORG> <ORG> for the 1970 season .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> relocated to <LOC> <LOC> , <LOC> and became the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> for the 2008 – 09 season ..",
        "score": 0.898,
        "id": 743
    },
    {
        "s1": "In contrast , prospective memory is memory for future intentions , or remembering to remember ( <PER> , 1988 ) .",
        "s2": "Prospective memory can be further broken down into event - and time-based prospective remembering .",
        "score": 0.785,
        "id": 747
    },
    {
        "s1": "Stress has a significant effect on memory formation and learning .",
        "s2": "<PER> and <PER> <PER> demonstrates how learning under stress also decreases memory recall in humans .",
        "score": 0.8,
        "id": 753
    },
    {
        "s1": "Therefore , sleep has the greatest effect on memory consolidation .",
        "s2": "There have been several studies which show that sleep improves the retention of memory , as memories are enhanced through active consolidation .",
        "score": 0.915,
        "id": 755
    },
    {
        "s1": "Therefore , sleep has the greatest effect on memory consolidation .",
        "s2": "This process implicates that memories are reactivated during sleep , but that the process does n’t enhance every memory .",
        "score": 0.765,
        "id": 756
    },
    {
        "s1": "The top ten best-selling drugs of 2013 totaled $ 75.6 billion in sales , with the anti-inflammatory drug <MISC> being the best-selling drug worldwide at $ 10.7 billion in sales .",
        "s2": "The top three best-selling drugs in the <LOC> <LOC> in 2013 were <ORG> ($ 6.3 billion ,) <MISC> ($ 6 billion ) and <MISC> ($ 5.4 billion ) .",
        "score": 0.83,
        "id": 764
    },
    {
        "s1": "The top three best-selling drugs in the <LOC> <LOC> in 2013 were <ORG> ($ 6.3 billion ,) <MISC> ($ 6 billion ) and <MISC> ($ 5.4 billion ) .",
        "s2": "The best-selling drug ever , <MISC> , averaged $ 13 billion annually and netted $ 141 billion total over its lifetime before <ORG> 's patent expired in November 2011 ..",
        "score": 0.789,
        "id": 766
    },
    {
        "s1": "In <MISC> <MISC> , the word ' asphalt ' is used to refer to a mixture of mineral aggregate and asphalt / bitumen ( also called tarmac in common parlance ) .",
        "s2": "[ citation needed ] In <MISC> <MISC> , ' asphalt ' is equivalent to the <MISC> ' bitumen ' .",
        "score": 0.879,
        "id": 773
    },
    {
        "s1": "In <MISC> <MISC> , the word ' asphalt ' is used to refer to a mixture of mineral aggregate and asphalt / bitumen ( also called tarmac in common parlance ) .",
        "s2": "However , ' asphalt ' is also commonly used as a shortened form of ' asphalt concrete ' ( therefore equivalent to the <MISC> ' asphalt ' or ' tarmac ') .",
        "score": 0.876,
        "id": 774
    },
    {
        "s1": "[ citation needed ] In <MISC> <MISC> , ' asphalt ' is equivalent to the <MISC> ' bitumen ' .",
        "s2": "In <MISC> <MISC> , bitumen is often used as the generic term for road surfaces .",
        "score": 0.829,
        "id": 777
    },
    {
        "s1": "[ citation needed ] In <MISC> <MISC> , ' asphalt ' is equivalent to the <MISC> ' bitumen ' .",
        "s2": "However , ' asphalt ' is also commonly used as a shortened form of ' asphalt concrete ' ( therefore equivalent to the <MISC> ' asphalt ' or ' tarmac ') .",
        "score": 0.819,
        "id": 776
    },
    {
        "s1": "1848 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1850 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.893,
        "id": 796
    },
    {
        "s1": "1846 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1848 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.888,
        "id": 793
    },
    {
        "s1": "1843 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1848 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.881,
        "id": 786
    },
    {
        "s1": "1850 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1853 ) and <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.878,
        "id": 798
    },
    {
        "s1": "1843 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1853 ) and <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.87,
        "id": 788
    },
    {
        "s1": "1843 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1850 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.854,
        "id": 787
    },
    {
        "s1": "1846 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1850 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.854,
        "id": 794
    },
    {
        "s1": "1843 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1846 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.854,
        "id": 785
    },
    {
        "s1": "1841 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1843 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.84,
        "id": 778
    },
    {
        "s1": "1848 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1853 ) and <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.837,
        "id": 797
    },
    {
        "s1": "1843 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1844 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.837,
        "id": 784
    },
    {
        "s1": "1844 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1848 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.834,
        "id": 790
    },
    {
        "s1": "1841 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1846 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.831,
        "id": 780
    },
    {
        "s1": "1844 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1846 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.827,
        "id": 789
    },
    {
        "s1": "1846 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1853 ) and <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.826,
        "id": 795
    },
    {
        "s1": "1841 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1848 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 781
    },
    {
        "s1": "1844 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1853 ) and <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.814,
        "id": 792
    },
    {
        "s1": "1844 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1850 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.81,
        "id": 791
    },
    {
        "s1": "1841 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1853 ) and <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.806,
        "id": 783
    },
    {
        "s1": "1841 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1850 ) , <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.794,
        "id": 782
    },
    {
        "s1": "The area of <LOC> and the <LOC> <LOC> has a semi-arid climate with hot summers , cool winters and fewer rainy days than the <MISC> climate .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> <LOC> and the <LOC> areas have desert climate with very hot and dry summers , and mild winters with few days of rain .",
        "score": 0.893,
        "id": 803
    },
    {
        "s1": "Coastal areas , such as those of <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> , have a typical <MISC> climate with cool , rainy winters and long , hot summers .",
        "s2": "The area of <LOC> and the <LOC> <LOC> has a semi-arid climate with hot summers , cool winters and fewer rainy days than the <MISC> climate .",
        "score": 0.804,
        "id": 801
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> , the <ORG> <ORG> , and the <ORG> <ORG> consistently ranked among world 's 100 top universities by the prestigious <ORG> academic ranking .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> and <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> are ranked among the world 's top 100 universities by <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> magazine .",
        "score": 0.895,
        "id": 805
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> , the <ORG> <ORG> , and the <ORG> <ORG> consistently ranked among world 's 100 top universities by the prestigious <ORG> academic ranking .",
        "s2": "<LOC> 's seven research universities ( excluding the <ORG> <ORG> ) are consistently ranked among top 500 in the world ..",
        "score": 0.823,
        "id": 806
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> is also the third-largest <MISC> economic partner of <LOC> and the two countries have military as well as extensive space technology ties .",
        "s2": "<LOC> is one of the few majority <MISC> countries to develop bilateral strategic and economic relations with <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.808,
        "id": 809
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> is one of the few majority <MISC> countries to develop bilateral strategic and economic relations with <LOC> .",
        "s2": "In <LOC> , <LOC> is <LOC> 's main and closest ally in the continent due to common political , religious and security interests .",
        "score": 0.774,
        "id": 810
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> were a hellenized <MISC> family from <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The peoples around <LOC> <LOC> , known as the <MISC> , were intermixed and <MISC> <MISC> ..",
        "score": 0.798,
        "id": 814
    },
    {
        "s1": "However , the massive migration of northern <MISC> <MISC> into <LOC> region mainly occurred after the <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> court fled from the north to the south , causing large numbers of northern <MISC> <MISC> to move into <LOC> region .",
        "score": 0.811,
        "id": 827
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> <MISC> ( <MISC> ) is a hybrid of the <LOC> and <LOC> dialects .",
        "s2": "<MISC> is also a hybrid of these two dialects .",
        "score": 0.888,
        "id": 829
    },
    {
        "s1": "The population had declined since the previous census carried out in 1996 , with an average annual growth rate of − 1.5 per thousand .",
        "s2": "Continual decline has been documented since the census period of 1975 – 1985 , which showed a rate of − 5.6 per thousand .",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 832
    },
    {
        "s1": "Notable restaurants in <LOC> include <LOC> atop the <LOC> <LOC> , widely regarded to be the finest restaurant in the city .",
        "s2": "Numerous restaurants are located along the <LOC> of <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.805,
        "id": 837
    },
    {
        "s1": "The share of <MISC> loanwords is about 1.5 % , but this number is still on the increase .",
        "s2": "Conversely , <MISC> contributed many loanwords to <MISC> , accounting for 1.3 % ..",
        "score": 0.817,
        "id": 850
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> vocabulary is predominantly <MISC> in origin , with an additional share of loanwords of 20 % .",
        "s2": "The share of <MISC> loanwords is about 1.5 % , but this number is still on the increase .",
        "score": 0.771,
        "id": 848
    },
    {
        "s1": "Clothing protects against many things that might injure the uncovered human body .",
        "s2": "Some clothing protects from specific environmental hazards , such as insects , noxious chemicals , weather , weapons , and contact with abrasive substances .",
        "score": 0.887,
        "id": 855
    },
    {
        "s1": "Clothes protect people from the elements , including rain , snow , wind , and other weather , as well as from the sun .",
        "s2": "Some clothing protects from specific environmental hazards , such as insects , noxious chemicals , weather , weapons , and contact with abrasive substances .",
        "score": 0.811,
        "id": 856
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> compete in <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> ( <ORG> ) as a members of the <MISC> <MISC> ( <ORG> ) Central division ; the team plays its home baseball games at <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> are also one of two active major league teams based in <LOC> ; the other is the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> , who are a member of the <MISC> <MISC> ( <LOC> ) Central division .",
        "score": 0.868,
        "id": 859
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> <ORG> are an <MISC> professional baseball team located on the <LOC> <LOC> of <LOC> , <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> compete in <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> ( <ORG> ) as a members of the <MISC> <MISC> ( <ORG> ) Central division ; the team plays its home baseball games at <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.848,
        "id": 857
    },
    {
        "s1": "In even numbered years , the <ORG> <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "s2": "In odd numbered years , the <MISC> <MISC> had home field advantage .",
        "score": 0.752,
        "id": 862
    },
    {
        "s1": "Odd numbered years the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "s2": "Even numbered years the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "score": 0.981,
        "id": 864
    },
    {
        "s1": "In the 1982 <MISC> <MISC> the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> of the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "s2": "In the 1983 <MISC> <MISC> the <ORG> <ORG> of the <ORG> had home field advantage ..",
        "score": 0.974,
        "id": 869
    },
    {
        "s1": "Even numbered years the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "s2": "In the 1982 <MISC> <MISC> the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> of the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "score": 0.816,
        "id": 867
    },
    {
        "s1": "Even numbered years the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "s2": "In the 1983 <MISC> <MISC> the <ORG> <ORG> of the <ORG> had home field advantage ..",
        "score": 0.797,
        "id": 868
    },
    {
        "s1": "Odd numbered years the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "s2": "In the 1982 <MISC> <MISC> the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> of the <ORG> had home field advantage .",
        "score": 0.796,
        "id": 865
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> had his first of four multi-home run games that month on June 1 , and went on to break <PER> <PER> 's record with 20 home runs in the month , a record that still stands .",
        "s2": "By the end of his historic month , the outfielder 's 33 home runs tied him with <PER> <PER> , <PER> and left him only four behind <PER> 's 37 .",
        "score": 0.79,
        "id": 873
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> had 13 home runs entering the month , representing less than half of <PER> <PER> 's total .",
        "s2": "<PER> had his first of four multi-home run games that month on June 1 , and went on to break <PER> <PER> 's record with 20 home runs in the month , a record that still stands .",
        "score": 0.774,
        "id": 872
    },
    {
        "s1": "The terms piracy and theft are often associated with copyright infringement .",
        "s2": "The original meaning of piracy is \" robbery or illegal violence at sea \" , but the term has been in use for centuries as a synonym for acts of copyright infringement .",
        "score": 0.801,
        "id": 883
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.965,
        "id": 896
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.951,
        "id": 887
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.945,
        "id": 915
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.933,
        "id": 888
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.933,
        "id": 904
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.93,
        "id": 897
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.926,
        "id": 926
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.92,
        "id": 922
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.917,
        "id": 908
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.917,
        "id": 889
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.914,
        "id": 927
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.906,
        "id": 923
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.901,
        "id": 900
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "score": 0.899,
        "id": 890
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.893,
        "id": 931
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.892,
        "id": 929
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.889,
        "id": 894
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.888,
        "id": 901
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "score": 0.881,
        "id": 898
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.879,
        "id": 902
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.879,
        "id": 924
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.872,
        "id": 909
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.87,
        "id": 914
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "score": 0.87,
        "id": 911
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.869,
        "id": 892
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.867,
        "id": 893
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "score": 0.866,
        "id": 905
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.863,
        "id": 907
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.861,
        "id": 921
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.857,
        "id": 916
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.855,
        "id": 928
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "score": 0.854,
        "id": 891
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.851,
        "id": 913
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; and 5 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "score": 0.851,
        "id": 912
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.85,
        "id": 925
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "score": 0.846,
        "id": 899
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 20 %) ; 2 .",
        "score": 0.843,
        "id": 906
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 23 %) ; and 5 .",
        "score": 0.834,
        "id": 920
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 93 %) ; 2 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.834,
        "id": 895
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.826,
        "id": 930
    },
    {
        "s1": "According to a 2007 <ORG> and <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> ( <ORG> ) study , the five countries with the highest rates of software piracy were : 1 .",
        "s2": "According to the study 's results , the five countries with the lowest piracy rates were : 1 .",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 886
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 3 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.82,
        "id": 903
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 21 %) ; 3 .",
        "score": 0.816,
        "id": 918
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 92 %) ; 4 .",
        "s2": "<LOC> ( 25 %) .",
        "score": 0.811,
        "id": 910
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> ( 91 %) .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> ( 22 %) ; 4 .",
        "score": 0.809,
        "id": 919
    },
    {
        "s1": "and in March 1604 Sir <PER> <PER> commanded the second voyage .",
        "s2": "General <PER> <PER> , a captain during the second voyage , led the third voyage from 1607 to 1610 ..",
        "score": 0.778,
        "id": 943
    },
    {
        "s1": "Sir <PER> <PER> commanded the first <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> voyage in 1601 and returned in 1603.",
        "s2": "and in March 1604 Sir <PER> <PER> commanded the second voyage .",
        "score": 0.773,
        "id": 941
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> is predominant in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<MISC> is predominant in the <LOC> , eastern <LOC> , <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.932,
        "id": 949
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> is predominant in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> is also predominantly <MISC> <MISC> due to a history of <MISC> rule ..",
        "score": 0.866,
        "id": 951
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> is predominant in the <LOC> , eastern <LOC> , <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> is also predominantly <MISC> <MISC> due to a history of <MISC> rule ..",
        "score": 0.791,
        "id": 953
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> is predominant in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "The <LOC> has the largest <MISC> <MISC> population in <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.779,
        "id": 950
    },
    {
        "s1": "Most wrestling matches last for a set number of falls , with the first side to achieve the majority number of pinfalls , submissions , or countouts being the winner .",
        "s2": "Historically , matches were wrestled to 3 falls (\" best 2 out of 3 \") or 5 falls (\" best 3 out of 5 \") .",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 956
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> is located in the first section of <LOC> <LOC> in the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> is near the <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> in the <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.874,
        "id": 968
    },
    {
        "s1": "After the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> , <LOC> and <LOC> emerged as two competitors .",
        "s2": "<LOC> , trying to remain the dominant power in <LOC> <LOC> , led the way in the terms of the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "score": 0.781,
        "id": 969
    },
    {
        "s1": "The first , 18 <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The second , 18 <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.907,
        "id": 990
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> is the 22nd most extensive , the 3rd most populous , and the 8th most densely populated of the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> is the most populous city in <LOC> , and the largest city by area in the contiguous <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.801,
        "id": 991
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> has a large and diverse <MISC> population , with <MISC> and <MISC> <MISC> being the largest groups in the state .",
        "s2": "<LOC> has the second largest <MISC> <MISC> population after <LOC> <LOC> , as well as the fastest-growing in the nation .",
        "score": 0.833,
        "id": 996
    },
    {
        "s1": "It was later announced that Queen + <PER> <PER> would play two shows at the <ORG> <ORG> , <LOC> on 11 and 12 July 2012 .",
        "s2": "Queen also performed with <PER> on 3 July 2012 at <LOC> 's <LOC> <LOC> , and on 7 July 2012 at the <LOC> <LOC> in <LOC> , <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.789,
        "id": 1002
    },
    {
        "s1": "On 30 June , Queen + <PER> performed in <LOC> , <LOC> at a joint concert with <PER> <PER> for the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "Queen also performed with <PER> on 3 July 2012 at <LOC> 's <LOC> <LOC> , and on 7 July 2012 at the <LOC> <LOC> in <LOC> , <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.789,
        "id": 1003
    },
    {
        "s1": "A version of \" <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> \" by <PER> <PER> was in the 2004 film <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "s2": "In 2001 , a version of \" <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> \" was performed by <PER> <PER> and <PER> <PER> in the film musical <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.82,
        "id": 1006
    },
    {
        "s1": "In June 2010 , the choir performed \" <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> \" in the episode \" <MISC> \" .",
        "s2": "In May 2012 , the choir performed \" <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> \" in the episode \" <MISC> \" , and the song features in <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> ..",
        "score": 0.952,
        "id": 1009
    },
    {
        "s1": "In June 2010 , the choir performed \" <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> \" in the episode \" <MISC> \" .",
        "s2": "The following week 's episode , \" <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> \" , features a rival choir performing \" <MISC> <MISC> \" in its entirety .",
        "score": 0.879,
        "id": 1008
    },
    {
        "s1": "The altar is called the communion table and the altar area is called the Chancel by <MISC> .",
        "s2": "In a <MISC> ( <ORG> <ORG> ) there may be an altar cross , either on the communion table or on a table in the chancel .",
        "score": 0.832,
        "id": 1013
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <ORG> <ORG> church in <LOC> was influenced by <PER> <PER> and the <ORG> <ORG> church <LOC> and has around 1 800 members .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> in <LOC> was founded in 1903 by pastor <PER> , has 500 congregations and 75 000 members .",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 1015
    },
    {
        "s1": "A number of partnerships exist between presbyteries in <LOC> and the <ORG> ( <LOC> ) , including specific connections with <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "For example , the <ORG> <ORG> , located in <LOC> <LOC> , has a partnership with a presbytery in <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.863,
        "id": 1016
    },
    {
        "s1": "Many predators specialize in hunting only one species of prey .",
        "s2": "Some predators specialize in certain classes of prey , not just single species .",
        "score": 0.857,
        "id": 1024
    },
    {
        "s1": "Predators may be put to use in conservation efforts to control introduced species .",
        "s2": "Predators from its natural range may be introduced to control populations , though in some cases this has little effect , and may even cause unforeseen problems .",
        "score": 0.764,
        "id": 1027
    },
    {
        "s1": "Besides their use in conservation biology , predators are also important for controlling pests in agriculture .",
        "s2": "Natural predators are an environmentally friendly and sustainable way of reducing damage to crops , and are one alternative to the use of chemical agents such as pesticides ..",
        "score": 0.763,
        "id": 1029
    },
    {
        "s1": "Biological classification is the method by which botanists group organisms into categories such as genera or species .",
        "s2": "Biological classification is a form of scientific taxonomy .",
        "score": 0.835,
        "id": 1038
    },
    {
        "s1": "Large <MISC> communities are in the north-western boroughs of <LOC> and <LOC> , the latter of which is home to <LOC> 's largest <MISC> temple , <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "There are <MISC> communities in East and <LOC> <LOC> , particularly in <LOC> , home to one of the largest <MISC> populations and the largest <MISC> temple outside <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.856,
        "id": 1048
    },
    {
        "s1": "There are large <MISC> communities in the eastern boroughs of <LOC> <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Large <MISC> communities are in the north-western boroughs of <LOC> and <LOC> , the latter of which is home to <LOC> 's largest <MISC> temple , <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.848,
        "id": 1046
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <LOC> <LOC> uses officially <LOC> , although its <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> mentions both <LOC> and <LOC> on its website .",
        "s2": "The <ORG> <ORG> uses <LOC> , as do the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , and <LOC> ..",
        "score": 0.884,
        "id": 1057
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <LOC> form an estimated 68 % of the population .",
        "s2": "10 % of the population are <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.819,
        "id": 1058
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> is home to four major language families : <MISC> , Tai – <MISC> , <MISC> , and <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The primary Tai – <MISC> language is <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 1060
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> is home to four major language families : <MISC> , Tai – <MISC> , <MISC> , and <MISC> .",
        "s2": "Mon , <LOC> , and <LOC> are the major <MISC> languages spoken in <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.783,
        "id": 1061
    },
    {
        "s1": "Mon , <LOC> , and <LOC> are the major <MISC> languages spoken in <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Little known fact about <LOC> is there are more than 130 languages spoken by people in <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.772,
        "id": 1063
    },
    {
        "s1": "Others , such as in the <MISC> communities of <LOC> , were speaking <MISC> and <MISC> , the languages of the <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "s2": "These languages were also used by the <MISC> of <LOC> at that time.",
        "score": 0.788,
        "id": 1066
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some <MISC> languages , particularly <MISC> and <MISC> , are also widely used .",
        "s2": "For example , in <LOC> , the <MISC> majority has adopted <MISC> , while the <MISC> minority uses <MISC> as its primary language .",
        "score": 0.784,
        "id": 1069
    },
    {
        "s1": "The three most commonly spoken languages among <MISC> today are <MISC> , <MISC> , and <MISC> .",
        "s2": "Some <MISC> languages , particularly <MISC> and <MISC> , are also widely used .",
        "score": 0.783,
        "id": 1068
    },
    {
        "s1": "<ORG> cotton acreage in <LOC> grew at a rapid rate , increasing from 50,000 hectares in 2002 to 10.6 million hectares in 2011 .",
        "s2": "The total cotton area in <LOC> was 12.1 million hectares in 2011 , so <ORG> cotton was grown on 88 % of the cotton area .",
        "score": 0.84,
        "id": 1074
    },
    {
        "s1": "The majority of video compression algorithms use lossy compression .",
        "s2": "As in all lossy compression , there is a trade-off between video quality , cost of processing the compression and decompression , and system requirements .",
        "score": 0.768,
        "id": 1081
    },
    {
        "s1": "Pesticides are used to control organisms that are considered to be harmful .",
        "s2": "Pesticides can prevent sickness in humans that could be caused by moldy food or diseased produce .",
        "score": 0.753,
        "id": 1085
    },
    {
        "s1": "Quarries at <ORG> supplied freestone used in the construction of <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Its quarries also supplied a cement factory at <LOC> , adjacent to the <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.786,
        "id": 1088
    },
    {
        "s1": "In 2004 , Provost <PER> <PER> became the President of the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "In 2007 Deputy Provost <PER> <PER> was named President of <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "score": 0.89,
        "id": 1094
    },
    {
        "s1": "In 2002 Provost <PER> <PER> became the Vice Chancellor of the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "s2": "In 2004 , Provost <PER> <PER> became the President of the <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> <ORG> .",
        "score": 0.814,
        "id": 1092
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> political philosophy dates back to the <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> , specifically with <MISC> in the 6th century <MISC> .",
        "s2": "<MISC> was the dominant political philosophy of the <MISC> <MISC> , but was replaced by <MISC> <MISC> in the <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.892,
        "id": 1101
    },
    {
        "s1": "The major philosophies during the period , <MISC> , <MISC> , <MISC> , <MISC> and <MISC> , each had a political aspect to their philosophical schools .",
        "s2": "Philosophers such as <MISC> , <PER> , and <MISC> , focused on political unity and political stability as the basis of their political philosophies .",
        "score": 0.776,
        "id": 1102
    },
    {
        "s1": "Although an alloy is technically an impure metal , when referring to alloys , the term \" impurities \" usually denotes those elements which are not desired .",
        "s2": "Conversely , otherwise pure-metals that simply contain unwanted impurities are often called \" impure metals \" and are not usually referred to as alloys .",
        "score": 0.881,
        "id": 1107
    },
    {
        "s1": "This is called a substitutional alloy .",
        "s2": "This is referred to as an interstitial alloy .",
        "score": 0.806,
        "id": 1110
    },
    {
        "s1": "<PER> <PER> <PER> is an internationally recognised poet and artist .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> <PER> is an artist and writer .",
        "score": 0.837,
        "id": 1117
    },
    {
        "s1": "His immediate successor , <PER> <PER> , who took the name <PER> <PER> <PER> , was created a cardinal in the consistory of 5 March 1973 .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> was created a cardinal in the consistory of 26 June 1967 .",
        "score": 0.778,
        "id": 1118
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> were the largest single group of foreigners with 15.6 % of total foreign population .",
        "s2": "Immigrants from <LOC> <LOC> , most of them former <MISC> refugees , were the largest group among people of <MISC> origin ( 6.3 %) .",
        "score": 0.759,
        "id": 1128
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> <MISC> are , roughly speaking , a large group of words typical of <MISC> Standard <MISC> , which do not appear either in <MISC> <MISC> , nor in other <MISC> dialects .",
        "s2": "The most frequent characteristics of <MISC> are in vocabulary , phrases , and pronunciation , but certain <MISC> denote themselves as special in syntax and orthography likewise .",
        "score": 0.822,
        "id": 1132
    },
    {
        "s1": "The principal official languages ( <MISC> , <MISC> , and <MISC> ) have terms , not used outside of <LOC> , known as <MISC> .",
        "s2": "The <MISC> spoken in <LOC> has similar terms , which are equally known as <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.805,
        "id": 1130
    },
    {
        "s1": "Dietary fiber is a carbohydrate that is incompletely absorbed in humans and in some animals .",
        "s2": "Dietary fiber consists mainly of cellulose , a large carbohydrate polymer which is indigestible as humans do not have the required enzymes to disassemble it .",
        "score": 0.823,
        "id": 1136
    },
    {
        "s1": ", weakly inflammatory PGE3 ) .",
        "s2": "pro-inflammatory PGE 2 ) .",
        "score": 0.833,
        "id": 1140
    },
    {
        "s1": "For the continued normal cellular maintenance , growth , and division , these free radicals must be sufficiently neutralized by antioxidant compounds .",
        "s2": "Some antioxidants are more effective than others at neutralizing different free radicals .",
        "score": 0.805,
        "id": 1141
    },
    {
        "s1": "Some antioxidants are more effective than others at neutralizing different free radicals .",
        "s2": "When interacting with a free radical , some antioxidants produce a different free radical compound that is less dangerous or more dangerous than the previous compound .",
        "score": 0.801,
        "id": 1142
    },
    {
        "s1": "2.",
        "s2": "3.",
        "score": 0.903,
        "id": 1153
    },
    {
        "s1": "3.",
        "s2": "4.",
        "score": 0.897,
        "id": 1155
    },
    {
        "s1": "2.",
        "s2": "4.",
        "score": 0.881,
        "id": 1154
    },
    {
        "s1": "1.",
        "s2": "2.",
        "score": 0.841,
        "id": 1150
    },
    {
        "s1": "1.",
        "s2": "3.",
        "score": 0.818,
        "id": 1151
    },
    {
        "s1": "“ The roots of all our modern academic fields can be found within the pages of literature .",
        "s2": "It is easy to see how all academic fields have roots in literature .",
        "score": 0.818,
        "id": 1157
    },
    {
        "s1": "Collectively , they are known as <MISC> characters .",
        "s2": "In <MISC> , they are sometimes called <MISC> characters .",
        "score": 0.865,
        "id": 1165
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> characters are logograms used in the writing of <MISC> and some other <MISC> languages .",
        "s2": "In <MISC> , they are sometimes called <MISC> characters .",
        "score": 0.844,
        "id": 1163
    },
    {
        "s1": "<MISC> characters are logograms used in the writing of <MISC> and some other <MISC> languages .",
        "s2": "Collectively , they are known as <MISC> characters .",
        "score": 0.788,
        "id": 1162
    },
    {
        "s1": "The art of writing <MISC> characters is called <MISC> calligraphy .",
        "s2": "In ancient <LOC> , <MISC> calligraphy is one of the Four Arts of the <MISC> <MISC> .",
        "score": 0.803,
        "id": 1169
    },
    {
        "s1": "Those identifying with <MISC> ancestry dropped by 1 % to 11 % ( although those born in <LOC> remain the largest non-native group at 3,942 persons ) .",
        "s2": "Those who reported <MISC> <MISC> ancestry were 13 % .",
        "score": 0.782,
        "id": 1175
    },
    {
        "s1": "About 46 % of the population identified themselves with <MISC> ancestry in 2010 , which was a decrease from the 51 % who did so in the 2000 census .",
        "s2": "Those identifying with <MISC> ancestry dropped by 1 % to 11 % ( although those born in <LOC> remain the largest non-native group at 3,942 persons ) .",
        "score": 0.777,
        "id": 1173
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> also competed in <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> at the 2006 <MISC> <MISC> in <LOC> , <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<PER> <PER> competed in the <LOC> <MISC> in 2008 .",
        "score": 0.843,
        "id": 1177
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> also competed in <MISC> <MISC> <MISC> at the 2006 <MISC> <MISC> in <LOC> , <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> also competes in the biennial <MISC> <MISC> , which it hosted in 2013 ..",
        "score": 0.78,
        "id": 1178
    },
    {
        "s1": "The <MISC> film industry is known as <MISC> ( a portmanteau of <LOC> and <LOC> ) and is now the 2nd-largest producer of movies in the world .",
        "s2": "<MISC> cinema is <LOC> 's largest movie industry in terms of both value and the number of movies produced per year .",
        "score": 0.839,
        "id": 1184
    },
    {
        "s1": "1898 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1902 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.9,
        "id": 1196
    },
    {
        "s1": "1885 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1902 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.899,
        "id": 1194
    },
    {
        "s1": "1902 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1908 ) , and <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.891,
        "id": 1198
    },
    {
        "s1": "1885 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1898 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.88,
        "id": 1193
    },
    {
        "s1": "1881 ) , <PER> <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1885 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.877,
        "id": 1189
    },
    {
        "s1": "1898 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1908 ) , and <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.87,
        "id": 1197
    },
    {
        "s1": "1885 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1908 ) , and <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.869,
        "id": 1195
    },
    {
        "s1": "1881 ) , <PER> <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1898 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.863,
        "id": 1190
    },
    {
        "s1": "1881 ) , <PER> <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "s2": "1902 ) , <PER> <PER> ( b.",
        "score": 0.855,
        "id": 1191
    },
    {
        "s1": "Hence , ɸ can verify neither the proposition \" the spin in the direction of y is positive \" nor the proposition \" the spin in the direction of y is negative .",
        "s2": "\" Nevertheless , the disjunction of the propositions \" the spin in the direction of y is positive or the spin in the direction of y is negative \" must be true for ɸ .",
        "score": 0.855,
        "id": 1200
    },
    {
        "s1": "Voltage reversal is encountered in <ORG> circuits that are under-damped .",
        "s2": "In comparison , critically damped or over-damped systems usually do not experience a voltage reversal .",
        "score": 0.797,
        "id": 1206
    },
    {
        "s1": "Capacitors may have their connecting leads arranged in many configurations , for example axially or radially .",
        "s2": "The leads ( until bent ) are usually in planes parallel to that of the flat body of the capacitor , and extend in the same direction ; they are often parallel as manufactured ..",
        "score": 0.76,
        "id": 1208
    },
    {
        "s1": "Crevasses form due to differences in glacier velocity .",
        "s2": "If two rigid sections of a glacier move at different speeds and directions , shear forces cause them to break apart , opening a crevasse .",
        "score": 0.791,
        "id": 1218
    },
    {
        "s1": "When a glacier moves through irregular terrain , cracks called crevasses develop in the fracture zone .",
        "s2": "Crevasses form due to differences in glacier velocity .",
        "score": 0.758,
        "id": 1216
    },
    {
        "s1": "Transverse crevasses are transverse to flow and form where steeper slopes cause a glacier to accelerate .",
        "s2": "Longitudinal crevasses form semi-parallel to flow where a glacier expands laterally .",
        "score": 0.828,
        "id": 1219
    },
    {
        "s1": "Longitudinal crevasses form semi-parallel to flow where a glacier expands laterally .",
        "s2": "Marginal crevasses form from the edge of the glacier , due to the reduction in speed caused by friction of the valley walls .",
        "score": 0.804,
        "id": 1221
    },
    {
        "s1": "Extensive glaciers are found in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> has glaciers on <LOC> <LOC> in <LOC> , on <LOC> <LOC> and in the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.879,
        "id": 1225
    },
    {
        "s1": "Extensive glaciers are found in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "Mountain glaciers are widespread , especially in the <LOC> , the <LOC> , the <LOC> <LOC> , the <LOC> , and the <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.877,
        "id": 1222
    },
    {
        "s1": "Mountain glaciers are widespread , especially in the <LOC> , the <LOC> , the <LOC> <LOC> , the <LOC> , and the <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> has glaciers on <LOC> <LOC> in <LOC> , on <LOC> <LOC> and in the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.814,
        "id": 1228
    },
    {
        "s1": "Extensive glaciers are found in <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> , <LOC> and <LOC> .",
        "s2": "<LOC> <LOC> currently contains no glaciers , although a small glacier on <LOC> <LOC> was present in the last glacial period .",
        "score": 0.814,
        "id": 1223
    },
    {
        "s1": "<LOC> <LOC> currently contains no glaciers , although a small glacier on <LOC> <LOC> was present in the last glacial period .",
        "s2": "<LOC> has glaciers on <LOC> <LOC> in <LOC> , on <LOC> <LOC> and in the <LOC> <LOC> .",
        "score": 0.784,
        "id": 1230
    },
    {
